The Charles Shackford Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, 1952-1980; Series III; .8' (2 boxes)
  - Correspondence to Charles Shackford, III.B
    - Kwartin, Paul, 1976-1978; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Lawrence College (Box 17, Folder 47)
      See: Smith, Daniel P.
    - Lieberman, Joseph L., 1975 Apr. 2 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Livermore, Nancy, [ca. 1970]; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Lockwood, Lewis (Box 17, Folder 47)
      See: II. Writings by Charles Shackford. "Imitiatio" in Dufay's missa Se la face ay pale.
    - Lord, Brian, 1970 Dec. 2; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Lustig, Leila S., 1978 Aug. 17; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Marlboro Festival (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - McClanahan, Richard, 1976 Aug. 1; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - McDaniel, Joseph M., Jr. (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - McKinley, Carl, 1956 May 17; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - McPhee, John, 1971-1977; 5 items (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Marriner, Neville, 1979 Nov. 5; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Miller, Carl S., 1946-1977; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Minnesota Orchestra, 1978 Dec. 20; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 49)
      See also: Marriner, Neville and Skrowaczewski, Stanislaw.
    - Moore, Paul, Jr., 1973 Jan. 2; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - [Music Mountain], 1978 July 9; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 49)
      See also: Kobler, Don and Rossi, Urico.
    - Newcomb, Anthony, 1974 May 20; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Newton-Wellesley Hospital (Box 17, Folder 50)
      See: Fuller, Myrtice F.
    - The New Yorker, 1965-[ca. 1970]; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Noss, Luther, 1961 Sept. 21; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Old South Church in Boston (Box 17, Folder 50)
      See: McKinley, Carl.
    - Ortel, Loyde, 1966 Nov. 2; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Palisca, Claude, 1962 June 21; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Parkes, Peter W., 1975 Nov. 25; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Phemister, William, 1977 June 11; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Philion, Thomas E., 1977 Nov. 17; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Pickering, Norman C., 1952 Mar. 21; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Piston, Walter, 1958-1975; 5 items (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Pollack, Howard, 1977 Sept.-Nov.; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Reeve, [Charles McCormick], 1945 Aug. 24; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Reinecke, Hans-Peter, 1961 Oct. 23; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 53)
      Charles Shackford's draft of response (?) laid in.
    - Richmann, Herbert E., 1957-1958; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Rolland, Paul, 1960 Feb. 29; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Rosenbaum, Robert E., 1969 May 23; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Rossi, Urico, 1966 Aug. 28; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Saint Thomas Church, New York (Box 17, Folder 54)
      See: Self, William.
    - Sargeant, Winthrop, 1964 Jan. 6; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Schirmer (Box 17, Folder 54)
      See: G. Schirmer, Inc.
    - Schneller, Richard F., 1977 Dec. 5; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Schultz, Theodore John, 1974-1979; 8 items (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Scolley, John, [ca. 1970]; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Self, William, 1965 Oct.-Nov.; 3 items (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Seng, Peter J., 1968 May 10; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Serkin, Rudolf, 1976 Aug. 18; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - [Sewall, Robert], 1961-1976; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - [Shackford, William M.], "Bill and Pat", [1973]; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Shain, Charles E., 1968-1971; 3 items (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Simms, Brian R., 1973 Jan.-Feb.; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Simonds, Bruce, 1042-1960; 7 items (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Skrowaczewski, Stanislaw, 1977 Aug. 17; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Smith, Carelton Sprague, 1955 Mar.-Oct.; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Smith College (Box 17, Folder 56)
      See: Stott, Helen B.
    - Smith, Connie (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Smith, Daniel P., 1962 Feb. 13; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Smith, W. Edwin, 1964 Nov. 18; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Springer, George P., 1956 Jan. 12; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Steifel, Catherine Pierson, 1978 Feb. 15; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Stoney, William, 1966 Dec. 3?; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Stott, Helen B., 1955 Sept. 15; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Strong, Bente, 1976 Sept. 9; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Sullivan, Raymond A., 1974 July-Oct.; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Tapley, Rolland S., 1971 Oct. 23; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Terras, Rita (Box 17, Folder 58)
      See: Deguise, [Pierre] and [Rita] Terras.
    - Thompson, Marcia T. (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Tillotson, Fredric, 1952 Dec. 26; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Translations Center [Brooklyn College] (Box 17, Folder 58)
      See: Sullivan, Raymonde A.
    - Twelve College Exchange, 1972 Sept. 13; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Unitarian Society of Wellesley (Box 17, Folder 59)
      See: Chirurg, Virginia B.
    - United States Air Force (Box 17, Folder 59)
      See: Atlas, David
    - United States Army Band (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - University of Southern California, Berkley (Box 17, Folder 59)
      See: Boyden, David B., Duckles, Vincent, and Newcomb, Anthony.
    - University of Hartford, 1970 Nov. 2; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - University of Michigan, Ann Arbor (Box 17, Folder 59)
      See: Berry, Wallace T.
    - Vadala, Christopher, 1973 Mar. 4; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Van Sickle, Howard M., 1958-1960; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Vosgerchian, Luise, 1979 Nov. 28; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - [Waite, William G.], 1960-1966; 6 items (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Walters, Larry, 1976-1978; 3 items (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Ward, W. Dixson, 1964 Mar. 30; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Weer, Russell, 1963 Apr. 29; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Weicker, Lowell, 1977 Dec. 12; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Weinrich, Carl, 1952 Sept.-Oct.; 2 items (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Wesleyan University, Connecticut (Box 17, Folder 61)
      See: Cronin, James E., Rosenbaum, Robert A., and Winslow, Richard K.
    - WFCR, Amherst (Box 17, Folder 61)
      See: Cohen, Arthur R. and d'Armand, John.
    - Whitaker, Rogers E.M., 1975 July 20; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - White, J. Paul, 1956 Mar. 11; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Wiles, Gordon P. (Box 17, Folder 62)
      See: II. Writings by Charles Shackford. What Tragedy?.
    - Wilson College (Box 17, Folder 62)
      See: Ashway, Mildred.
    - Wilson, Keith, 1960-1975; 3 items (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Winer, Karen, 1973 Jan. 14; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Winograd, Arthur, 1977 Apr. 22; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Winslow, Richard K., 1968 Feb. 1; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - [Woodworth, G. Wallace], "Woody", 1946-1956; 3 items (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - WSHP, Shippensburg, Pennsylvania (Box 17, Folder 63)
      See: Alan, Don.
    - W.W. Norton, 1972 June 16; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - WWUH, Hartford (Box 17, Folder 63)
      See: Lord, Brian.
    - Wyatt, Gertrude L., 1956 May 8; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Yale University (Box 17, Folder 63)
      See: Ducibella, Salvatore F., Forte, Allen, Miller, Carl S., Noss, Luther, Ortel, Loyde, Palisca, Claude, Simonds, Bruce, Steifel, Catherine Pierson, and Waite, William G.
    - Young, Elmore C., 1957 Dec. 3; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence from Jane Shackford, III.C
    - [Baxter], Lincoln, 1980 Feb. 19; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Brooks, Richard, 1979 Sept. 4; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Pickett, Lawrence K., 1979 Sept. 5; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Rey, Walter, 1980 Mar. 5; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence to Jane Shackford, III.D
    - Allen, Eugene W., 1980 Mar. 26; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Baxter, Lincoln (Box 17, Folder 65)
      See: I.C Music by Others. Cantata on psalm 100 new.
    - Brooks, Richard, 1979 June 13; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Brown, Howard Mayer, 1979 June 11; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Ell, Frank, 1979 May 21; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Hurwood, David, 1980 July 4; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Kimberly, Derek R., 1979 Sept. 28; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Pickett, Lawrence K., 1979 Apr. 30; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - [Sewall], Richard, 1979 Aug. 25; 1 item (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence between Others, III.E
    - Letters between correspondents other than Charles Shackford or Jane Shackford., 1958-1979; 7 items (Box 17, Folder 66)
- Programs, 1940-1980; Series IV; .6' (2 boxes)
  In addition to concert programs, Series IV includes announcements, invitations, church service programs, and program notes. It is divided into six subseries, of which the first (A. Music and Arrangements By Charles Shackford) is arranged alphabetically by title of work and chronologically within each title. The remaining subseries are arranged chronologically.
  - Music and Arrangements by Charles Shackford, IV.A
    - At the window, 1940 May 8; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - A bargain, 1941 Mar. 30; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 2)
      See also: Suites, Piano.
    - Behold how good and pleasant it is, 1970 Mar. 1; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Blessed is the man, 1972 Feb.-Apr.; 4 items (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Bless the Lord, O my soul., 1967-1979; 4 items (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Concerto, brasses, orchestra, 1978 Oct. 5; 2 items (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Duets, clarinets; arr., 1976 Apr. 25; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Eclogue, 1976-1978; 4 items (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Fantasies, violoncello, piano, F, 1963-1972; 3 items (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Fantasy on Vysehrad, 1969-1975; 2 items (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Follow thy fair sun, unhappy shadow (Box 18, Folder 10)
      See: At the window.
    - Son of God; arr., Gauntlett, Henry John (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Have mercy upon me, O God, [1962] Nov. 4; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - I was glad when they said unto me, 1973 Dec. 4; 3 items (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - I will lift up mine eyes, 1971 May 2; 2 items (Box 18, Folder 13)
      See also: Sonatas, organ and Nunc dimittises, mixed voices.
    - Lord is my shepherd, 1966-1970; 10 items (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Nunc dimittises, women's voices. English, 1964-1966; 5 items (Box 18, Folder 15-16)
    - Nunc dimittises, mixed voices. English, 1971 May 2; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 17)
      See also: Suites, piano, Toccata, brasses, and Psalm 5.
    - Ode to learning, 1960 June 10; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Once in royal David's city (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - O sing unto the Lord, 1968-1971; 7 items (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Overture concertante, 1975-1979; 7 items (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Psalm 5, 1964-1973; 6 items (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Psalm 107, 1959-1980; 3 items (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Psalm 139, 1978 Nov. 5; 3 items (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Quartets, strings, no. 1, A, 1977-1978; 5 items (Box 18, Folder 24)
      See also: Eclogue.
    - Quartets, strings, no. 2, C, 1979 Aug. 12; 2 items (Box 18, Folder 25)
      See also: Suites, piano.
    - Quintets, clarinet, horn, violin, viola, violoncello, E-flat, 1973-1979; 7 items (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Quintets, oboe, trumpet, saxophone, violoncello, double bass, G, 1974-1976; 3 items (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Serenades, harpsichord, flute, clarinet, D, 1975-1977; 5 items (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Sonatas, organ, 1957-1979; 3 items (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Suites, piano, 1970-1980; 6 items (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Te deum. English, 1956-1966; 5 items (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Toccata, brasses, 1967-1970; 3 items (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Trios, strings, A, 1948-1970; 4 items (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Trios, oboe, clarinet, bassoon, G, 1971-1979; 8 items (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Charles Shackford as Choral Conductor and Church Musician, IV.B
    - 1945-1959, 24 items (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - 1960-1972, 38 items (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Charles Shackford as Performer and Instrumental Conductor, IV.C
    - 1940-1972, 22 items (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Charles Shackford's Other Activities, IV.D
    - Papers, sermons, etc., 1966-1972; 11 items (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Music By Charles Shackford's Students, IV.E
    - 1979-1984, 3 items (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous, IV.F
    - 1940-1951, 25 items (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - 1952-1980, 28 items (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Photographs, 1942-1978; Series V; .6' (2 boxes)
  Subseries A. to D. are arranged chronologically.
  - Charles Shackford Alone, V.A
    - 1952-[ca. 1978], 5 items (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Charles Shackford and Others, V.B
    - Hindemith's class at Yale, acoustics research, Belmont Community Chorus, and Connecticut College., 1942-1973; 17 items (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Without Charles Shackford, V.C
    - Hindemith, acoustics, Belmont Community Chorus, and Connecticut College., 1942-1967; 16 items (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - TV Program on Elizabethan Music, V.D
    - "Photostatic negatives for TV program 'Music of Shakespeare's England' 8 Jan. 1964" --Container., 1964 Jan.; 42 items (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Student Materials, ca. 1934-1948; Series VI; 1.25' (3 boxes)
  Student Materials are divided into three subseries and are arranged chronologically.
  - High School, VI.A
    - Paper on railroads., [ca. 1934 (?)]; 1 item (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Yale and Juilliard, VI.B
    - History outlines., ca. 1937; 5 items (Box 20, Folder 2-3)
    - Juilliard assignments., ca. 1940 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Spiral bound notebooks., ca. 1940; 3 items (Box 20, Folder 5-7)
      "Music & Culture"--Covers.
    - Loose sheets., ca. 1943 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      "Notes from Hindemith"--Container.
    - Loose sheets., ca. 1943 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      "Papers for Kirkpatrick Bach course"--Container.
    - Loose sheets., ca. 1943 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      Reproductions of extracts from musicological original sources, examinations, etc.
      Includes Boethius, De institutione musica, chapter 34, Quid sit musicus, "Translated from ancient Latin by Charlie--Part of his Master of Music examination at Yale".
    - Loose sheets., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      "Shackford: Papers for course at Yale, 1942"--Container.
    - Loose sheets., ca. 1943 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      "Work with Hindemith at Yale (probably spring of '43 according to typed note by CRS)"--Container.
      Includes typescript reproductions of sheets explaining Hindemith's 3 part counterpoint.
  - Harvard, VI.C
    See also: I.A Music by Charles Shackford. Counterpoint with Walter Piston.
    - Loose sheets., 1946-1947 (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
      "Music 100a...Harvard...Fall term. 1946-1947".
    - Note book., ca. 1946; 1 item (Box 21, Folder 15)
      "Original Thesis I, Charles R. Shackford"--Cover.
    - Loose sheets., 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      Music history notes.
    - Loose sheets., ca. 1947 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Loose leaf note book., 1947-1948; 1 item (Box 22, Folder 18)
      "Harvard, Music 201-103, Notes & Reports".
    - Loose leaf note book., ca. 1947; 1 item (Box 22, Folder 19)
      "Harvard, Music 103b, Notes & Reports".
- Teaching Materials, 1944-1972; Series VII; .4' (1 box)
  Arranged chronologically.
  See also: I.A Music by Charles Shackford. Sketchbooks (ca. 1967).
  - Loose sheets., 1944-1946 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Bennett Junior College course material.
  - Loose sheets., 1945 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    "Student work, Bennett Junior College"--Container.
  - Loose sheets., 1963-1972 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Wilson College and Connnecticut College course material.
  - Loose sheets., [ca. 1965 (?)] (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Reproduction of a translation of St. Augustine's treatise on music.
  - Loose sheets., [ca. 1965 (?)] (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Musical examples (?).
  - Loose sheets., [ca. 1965 (?)] (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Paper comments.
- Biographical Material, Series VIII; .4' (1 box)
  - Bio-bibliographies., 1955-1982; 18 items (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Contains resumes, repertoire lists, list of compositions, the family's inventory of Charles Shackford's papers, biographical extracts, obituaries, etc.
- Memorabilia, 1937-1967; Series IX; .4' (1 box)
  - Acceptances, yearbook, poems by others, etc., 1937-1967; 13 items (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Clippings and Articles, 1945-1984; Series X; .4' (1 box)
  Series X comprises loose clippings, unclipped articles, etc. It is divided into six subseries, of which the first (A. Music by Charles Shackford) is arranged alphabetically by title of work. The remaining subseries are arranged chronologically.
  - Music by Charles Shackford, X.A
    - A bargain
      See: Suites, piano.
    - Blessed is the man, 1972 Winter-Sept.; 4 items (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Concerto, brasses, orchestra, 1977-1978; 10 items (Box 23, Folder 2)
      See also: Toccata, brasses and C. General Articles about Charles Shackford.
    - Eclogue, 1976-1979; 4 items (Box 23, Folder 3)
      See also: Quartets, strings, no.1, A.
    - Fantasy on Vyserad, 1969-1975; 6 items (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - I was glad when they said unto me, 1973 Dec.; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Lord is my shepherd, 1966-1969; 3 items (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Nunc dimittises (Box 23, Folder 6)
      See: Toccata, brasses.
    - Ode to Learning, 1960 Jan. 22; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - O sing unto the Lord, 1969 Winter; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Overture Concertante, 1974-1979; 12 items (Box 23, Folder 9)
      See also: Quartets, strings, no, 2, C.
    - Psalm 5, women's voices, 1965 Nov. 17; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Psalm 107 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Psalm 139, 1978 Nov.; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 11)
      See also: Concerto, brasses, orchestra.
    - Quartets, strings, no. 1, A, 1976-1982; 22 items (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Quartets, strings, no. 2, C, 1979 Aug.; 2 items (Box 23, Folder 13)
      See also: Toccata, brasses.
    - Quintets, clarinet, horn, violin, viola, violoncello, E-flat, 1973-1979; 21 items (Box 23, Folder 14)
      See also: Quartets, strings, no, 1, A.
    - Quintets, oboe, trumpet, saxophone, violoncello, double bass, G, 1976 Nov. 19; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 15)
      See also: Overture concertante.
    - Serenades, harpsichord, flute, clarinet, D, 1975-1977; 6 items (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Sonatas, organ, 1961 July; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Suites, piano, 1980 Apr. 12; 2 items (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Te deum, 1956 May; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 19)
      See also: Sonatas, organ.
    - Toccata, brasses, 1980 Apr 15; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Trios, oboe, clarinet, bassoon, G, 1984 Feb. 6; 1 item (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Trios, strings, A, 1970 July-Aug.; 3 items (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Charles Shackford's Other Activities, X.B
    - Articles on his conducting, playing, scholarly activities, etc., 1945-1978; 51 items (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - General Articles about Charles Shackford, X.C
    - 1970-1980, 7 items (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Obituaries and Memorials, X.D
    - 1978-1984, 6 items (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - On Hindemith, X.E
    - 1948-1959, 4 items (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous, X.F
    - Includes articles on Charles Shackford's students, [ca.1960 (?)]-1983; 16 items (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Miscellaneous Items, 1955-1973; Series XI; .4' (1 box)
  Miscellaneous items are divided into two subseries, of which the first (A. Dated Items) is arranged chronologically, and the second (B. Undated Items), randomly.
  - Dated Items, XI.A
    - Items relating to various activities., 1955-1973; 29 items (Box 23, Folder 1)
      For photograph of participants in the President's Conference, see: V.B. Photographs. Charles Shackford With Others.
  - Undated Items, XI.B
    - no date (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Sound Recordings, Series XII
  Recordings of live performances of much of Charles Shackford's music are to be found in the Historical Sound Recordings Collection at Yale.